

# Carolina do Amaral Frederico

**Date of birth:** 18/11/1996 | **Nationality:** Brazilian | **Gender:** Female | **Phone number:** 

(+351) 961185205 (Mobile) | Email address: carolinafrederico32@hotmail.com | Github:

https://github.com/carolf32

Address: Rua Padre Domingos Soares, 4770-881, Vila Nova de Famalicão, Portugal (Home)

### **ABOUT ME**

I'm a Full Stack developer with knowledge in technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, TypeScript, SASS, Tailwind CSS, NodeJS, ReactJS, PostgreSQL, REST API, Express, all of which are relevant technologies for both Front-End and Back-End web development.

I believe that my experience of over 3 years in the sales field has contributed to the development of valuable skills in communication, problem-solving, and teamwork. Additionally, I have learned to develop resilience and time management, which will certainly complement my technical skills in my new career in technology.

I am an Agricultural Engineer and currently, I have decided to direct my career towards web development, where I see a field full of opportunities for innovation and personal growth. Having worked in a technology startup environment and needing to thoroughly understand the product I was selling, I became increasingly interested in this area, leading to my career transition.

# EDUCATION AND TRAINING

09/2023 - 07/2024 Brazil

FULL STACK DEVELOPER Kenzie Academy

03/2014 - 06/2019 Brazil

AGRONOMIC ENGINEER Universidade Federal de Santa Catarina

06/2019 - 06/2021 Brazil

BUSINESS MANAGEMENT MBA Universidade Federal de São Paulo

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **PORTUGUESE** 

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C1	C1	B2	B2	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

## DIGITAL SKILLS

Web Technologies Fundamentals - HTML, CSS | SASS(SCSS) | Javascript / Typescript / Node / Express | Javascript(Nodejs, ExpressJs) | Node.Js, React.Js | BoostrapCSS, TailwindCSS | Rest-api | Experience in SQL and in ORM(Object relational mapper) | Data-bases | Node.js / Express | PostgreSQL and MariaDB

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

06/2023 - 04/2024 Brazil

### **CLOSER BURST MIDIA**

Responsible for closing high-value sales, developing negotiation strategies, and maintaining a solid relationship with clients. I was responsible for helping to double the company's monthly recurring revenue.

01/2021 - 06/2023 Brazil

# **CLOSER BEON**

Guiding leads through the final stage of the sales process to complete the purchase. Understanding the pains and needs of the leads and evaluating if they fit with Beon's solution. I created the first playbook for new SDRs in the company, aiming to standardize the training of new employees.

03/2021 - 01/2022 Brazil

### SALES DEVELOPMENT REPRESENTATIVE BEON

Initiate first contact with inbound and outbound leads, research leads for active prospecting, assist clients via phone, WhatsApp, and email, generate value for the product and qualify potential clients, schedule meetings for sales representatives, record interactions and ensure leads progress to the next stage of the sales funnel, manage CRM (Pipedrive).